# **Hunt Hung**

UIUX / Product Designer

### **INTRO**

I'm a product designer that crafts digital experience to empower people. I have 7+ years of related experience in the field covering not only designer's role but also web front-end development, coaching and recruitment.

I am capable of performing a wide variety of skills including visualisation, user testing, frontend coding, video editing, 3d rendering and more.

#### **PORTFOLIO**

hlh112.github.io/portfo

### CONTACT

mobile +852 93061692

email hunter252006@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS**

/ Design Thinking / HTML/CSS/JS

/ UX Research / React JS

/ Prototyping / SQL

/ Visual Design / Wordpress

/ 3D Rendering / Shopify

/ Motion Graphic / SEO

/ Photo Retouching

## INDUSTRIES COVERED

Crypto DeFi Construction Industry
Insurtech Event Management

Al-powered Apps Logistics

eCommerce Social Platform

Sports Gaming

### **TOOLS**

Figma Marvel App Rive App Maze Design Webflow Sketch Adobe XD Zeplin Overflow Photoshop Lottie Illustrator Blender 3D InDesign AfterEffect Spline Invision Excel

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Jumppoint - Product Designer

Nov 2023 - Present

Responsible for curating solutions to cope with pain points from different parties, safeguarding project deliveries by taking resources and time into account while performing design thinking. Investigating into any possible logical or system bugs to ensure outcome quality. Occasionally performing multi-role responsibilities is required including PM, QA and Ops.

# Oursky - Product Designer

Feb 2023 - Oct 2023

Mainly responsible for an Al-powered Saas. Duties include product revamping, feature ideation, user journey auditing, uiux research and solution design. Constantly drafting product roadmap with product owner to drive sales.

# Hedvig AB (Sweden) – Product Designer

Nov 2021 - Feb 2023

Responsible for collecting and adjusting user feedbacks on the product. Conducting workshop and ux research to review the product roadmap. Establishing house-keeping practices for cross-functional team collaboration.

# MANTRA DAO - UIUX Designer (Contract)

Jun 2021 - Nov 2021

Responsible for auditing the company existing UI performance. Study feedbacks from the community users and make instant adjustments. Set priority and practical deployment schedules with dev-team. Suggesting better workflow, housekeeping tools as well as rebuilding a scalable design system.

### Oursky - Product Designer

Nov 2018 - Mar 2021 (part-time from 2021 onwards)

Responsible in client engagement, clarifying business needs, drafting user flow, crafting UI and performing UIQA. Experience in various types of project rundown from MVP, POC, waterfall to agile.

### Firmstudio — Web Designer & Fn-Developer

Jan - Sep 2018

Responsible for graphic, ui design and web front-end development. Act as a bridge between design and development team to tackle difficulties encountered during design-to-fn transition.

# Creasant — Web Designer & Design Lead

Sep 2016 - Nov 2017

Responsible for ui design. Partnered with the developer team to cope with design constraints and to make instant design modifications. Also responsible for acquiring and supervising new hires.

# **EDUCATION**

## Hong Kong Polytechic University

BA (Hons) Design - Visual Communication

2012 - 2016